innohosting.com 2009-03-31

# Privacy Policy

InnoHosting Privacy Policy

InnoHosting is committed to protecting your personal information and respecting your privacy.

We will never sell, rent, or disclose your personally identifiable information to outside parties without your consent unless compelled by a court of law to do so. However we do reserve the right to disclose your requirement information (if you are a member) to industry professionals in order to get your job done if needed. We may send you e-mail regarding our new features, news, or other important update information. In any case, we will never disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties. We may use various methods to collect information including, cookies and/or IP addresses. 

Legal

It is important you are aware of the InnoHosting policies _before_ you purchase your hosting package. If you require clarification on anything mentioned, please contact InnoHosting as we will be happy to clairfy and elaborate!

What Our Customers Say:

I just want to give a big "Thank you" to Rameen, Chris and Crew. I've had a reseller account with Inno for about a year and half now and I couldn't be happier with my choice to join them. The support has been superb. The reaction times and overall service have been excellent. I am almost always expect to have a resolution within the hour I turn in my ticket.  
read more

All Hosting Plans Include:

  * 99.9 % Uptime Guarantee 
  * 24 x 7 Technical Support 
  * User-Friendly Control Panel 
  * mySQL Databases 
  * CGI-bin / PHP / Perl 
  * Frontpage Extensions 
  * Fantastico DeLuxe Installer 
  * 16 Day Money Back Policy 
  * RVSkins 
  * SiteBuilder
  * Ruby on Rails
